输入密码
音乐播放器
单身狗之歌
BGM ：CAN'T GET ENOUGH – Basenji
谷歌浏览器
邮件
紧急：加州艺术学院 录取通知
亲爱的  维纳斯,
再次恭喜被我校录取！这封邮件是提醒您,您的录取回复截止时间是明天
这也许将会是您人生崭新的开始.点击接受加入我们2020年的课程
点 击 接 受
点击 回复 或查看 之前的邮件
好吧
Okay.
致相关负责人,
很遗憾的通知您我将不会入学
因为我是个输不起的胆小鬼
而且我也不敢告诉我母亲我想永远地离开斯塔顿岛  KJAHBWEKJHBXCKVHJ
脸书有一条新消息
JP格雷罗刚在一条状态中@了你
加油  美洲狮队  为动员大会做好准备
感谢 维 德尔莫尼科 帮我拍的照片
写点评论吧...
点赞
西德尼 斯洛娜
发起通话
接受
拒绝
早安 你在干吗
Good morning. What you doin'?
除了视奸JP之外
Besides stalking jp, of course.
新建空白页
你想多了 我在看新闻
I'm reading the news, thank you very much.
哦 你在看新闻呀
Oh! You're reading the news.
你可真会说谎啊
You're such a good liar.
讲真 你怎么知道我在视奸JP
Seriously, how do you know I'm stalking jp?
因为我真的真的太了解你了
Because I know you very, very well.
对了 你告诉你妈加州艺术学院的事了么
Oh, wait! Did you tell your mom 'bout calarts yet?
告诉了
Yeah, I told her.
她对于我要搬到国家的另一头
She's super excited for me to move across the country
去一个昂贵的艺术学校感到很兴奋
and go to a really expensive art school.
真的吗
Really?
- 才没有  - 没有吗
- No. - No?
我还没
No, I haven't found...
我还没找到正确的时机
I haven't found the right time to tell her.
啊 玩命直播开始了
Oh! Nerve is starting.
抱歉 这个真的很重要
Sorry, this is really important.
玩命直播是啥
What's nerve?
是一个游戏 看这 戳那个视频
It's a game. Here, just click on the video.
玩命直播
欢                     迎
欢迎来到纽约市玩命直播
Welcome to nerve New York City.
玩命直播是一个24小时游戏
Nerve is a 24-hour game.
24               小时
开           放
就像真心话大冒险 但没有真心话
Like truth or dare, minus the truth.
观众需付费观看
Watchers pay to watch.
玩家赢得奖金和荣誉
Players play to win cash and glory.
你是观众还是玩家
Are you a watcher or a player?
这很酷 是吧
It's cool, right?
这看起来不太正规 它合法么
This looks very sketchy. Is this legal?
我也不知道 可能不合法
I don't know. Probably not.
玩命直播
观众
玩家
别管那些 快去注册观看起来 时间紧迫
Just do it. Just sign up and watch. Time's ticking.
好的 注册了 我正在注册账号来看你直播
Okay, signing up. Look, this is me signing up to watch you.
小维 你必须注册来看我
Vee! You have to sign up and watch me.
让我有观众真的很重要
It's very important that I have watchers.
嘿 我得下线了 我妈妈回来了
Hey. I gotta go, my mom just got home.
我吃了早餐就注册 我保证
I'll sign up after breakfast. I promise.
谢啦 爱你 一会儿见
Thank you. I love you. I'll see you in a little bit.
- 拜 - 拜
- Bye. - Bye.
我说 小西还没拿到任何大学的通知
I mean, Syd hasn't gotten into any schools yet.
她甚至毫不在乎这个
And she doesn't even care.
你知道啥 西德妮不必在意这个
You know what? Sydney doesn't have to care.
她有信托基金
She has a trust fund.
你有比那更有价值的东西
And you have something far more valuable than that.
又来了
Here we go.
你有动力 你很专心
You have drive, you have focus.
还有本地大学的奖学金
You have a scholarship to a local college.
即使我们负担不起宿舍费
And even though we can't afford the dorm,
你还有我做你的大学室友
you get to have me as your new college roommate.
其实我
Actually, I, um...
我有一个还不错的想法
I had kind of a cool idea about that.
如果我们重新装修一下迈克的房间
What if we fixed up Mike's room
然后放到airbnb短租网上
and listed you on airbnb or something?
或许我们是时候整理他的东西
Maybe it's time we finally go through his stuff
或许也可以把其中一部分捐给慈善机构
and maybe give some of it to goodwill.
我也能给你一些空间
And I could give you some space.
我不想要空间
I don't want space.
我只想要你在身边
I just want you.
好吧
Okay.
我走读完全没问题
I'm totally down with commuting. I can...
我还可以在渡船上看书
I can get my reading done on the ferry.
是吗
Yeah?
这样行得通 是吧
That'll work, right?
对
Yeah.
BGM ：KAMIKAZE – MØ
我们一起说“美洲狮加油” 1 2 3
Let's say, "Go cougars" On the count of 1, 2, 3.
美洲狮队加油
Go cougars!
冲啊 美洲狮
Let's go, cougars!
- 把变焦镜头给我 - 给
Hand me the zoom lens. Here.
如果年鉴上每一张照片上都是JP 格雷罗
Doesn't it feel a little unbalanced
会不会有点不公平
if every single yearbook photo is of jp guerrero?
那不能怪我 他就是队员啊
It's not my fault he's on the team.
拿着
Here.
伙计们 小心点 小心点
Okay, guys. Be careful, careful.
我们上 JP
Let's hit it, jp!
冲啊 冲 冲 冲
All right, let's go! Let's go! Come on!
注意点 小心点
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
你拍到了 你拍到了
You got it. Yeah, you got it.
好了 小心 小心
All right, be careful. Careful.
耶
Yeah!
美洲狮加油
Let's go, cougars!
让我们掌声欢迎西德妮 斯隆
Let's hear it for Sydney Sloane!
那个戴墨镜的女孩 美洲狮加油
The girl with the shades. Let's go, cougars.
哇哦 真可口
Ooh, yum!
美洲狮 加油
Let's go, cougars.
丽芙 丽芙
Liv! Liv!
拿出我们的本事 美洲狮
Show 'em what we got, cougars!
让我们开始拉拉队表演吧 你去哪 小西
Okay, let's play... Where you goin', Syd?
我们的拉拉队长不知道干啥去了
We've lost our cheerleader.
拿出我们的本事  录像准备
Okay, show 'em what we got, vhs!
准备好了吗 记得做什么吧
Are you ready? Remember what to do?
好了 好 你上线了
- Okay. - Okay. You're on!
嘿 观众们宝宝们好 这里是小西
Hey, watchers! It's Syd baby.
我就指望你们助我闯到最后一关
I'm counting on you to get me to the final round.
所以别让我失望
So don't let me down
我不会让你们失望 我保证
and I won't let you down, I promise.
冲啊 兄弟 拿出我们的本事
Go, dude! Show 'em what we got!
让他们看到斯塔顿岛人的本色
Show 'em what staten island's really about!
加油吧 宝贝
Go cheer, baby!
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
死宅
Nerd!
嗷 这屁股怎么样
Ooh! How 'bout that ass, though?
好 谢谢西德妮
Okay. Thank you, Sydney.
任务达成
啊 你们让我挑战吃狗粮
Ah... you guys dared me to eat dog food.
你可以做到的
You can do this!
这好恶心 好恶心  别去想它
This is so gross. This is so gross. Don't think about it.
很好 咽下去
Okay. Keep it in.
泰 瞧好了 观众们
Ty! Wassup, watchers?
任务达成
哦 钱来了 哇哦
Oh! Money, money! Oh. Whoa!
我现在有超多观众
I have so many watchers now.
你做到了 姑娘
Yeah, you do. Girl!
我就是想要进那个排行榜
I just need to get in that little box thing.
谁现在第一
Who's winning now?
看来 是一个叫瑞恩的家伙
Apparently, this guy named Ryan.
他好像是把花生酱抹在丁丁上
I guess he put peanut butter on his junk
然后让狗舔干净
and let his dog lick it off.
我也能做到
I could do that.
但是你没有狗
But you don't have a dog.
我还是可以啊
I could still do it.
也没有丁丁 丽芙
Or a dick, Liv.
哦 他们给你发来下一个大冒险了
Ooh, they're coming up with your next dare!
是什么 我需要那种能爆的
What is it? I need something flashy
像花生酱那种的挑战
like the peanut butter thing.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey.
天啊 真诡异
My god, how weird.
他们怎么知道你恐高的
How do they know you're afraid of heights?
- 啥 - 他们让你挑战高度
- What? - That's what they do.
那很简单
It's easy.
他们是从你的旧档案里提取的信息
They just take all your info from your old profiles
然后放到玩命直播里
and put it in your nerve profile.
这好吓人啊
That's so creepy.
你被停课了
You just got suspended.
我以为你已经不玩这个了
I thought you were done playing nerve.
才不呢
Hell no!
赢了西雅图市冠军的女孩现在有上百万的粉丝
The girl who won Seattle now has millions of followers.
她是Instagram上的红人
She is insta-famous.
- 谁在乎 - 我在乎 小维
- Who cares? - I care, vee.
我不指望你理解
I don't expect you to understand.
我迷恋刺激肾上腺素的事
I'm an adrenaline junkie.
你喜欢待在你的舒适圈 那很好
You like to stay within your comfort zone. That's fine.
才不是这样
That's not true.
我们还一起上过钢管舞课
What about that pole dancing class we took?
小维 是我拖着你去的 你就坐在角落里看着罢了
Vee, I dragged you there and you sat in the corner and watched.
我是一个视觉学习者
I'm a visual learner.
你怎么攻击她
Why are you attacking her?
- 我不是在攻击她 汤米 - 你在
- I'm not attacking her, Tommy. - Yeah, you are.
时光匆匆
Life is passing you by.
我们都需要偶尔冒险
You need to learn to take a few risks every once in a while.
我有冒险啊
I do take risks.
真的吗 好吧
Really? Okay. Fine.
假设你在玩玩命直播
Let's just say hypothetically you're playing nerve.
对于小维来说什么冒险挑战比较好
What'd be a good nerve dare for vee?
和JP亲热
Make out with jp.
慢慢来 先一小步
Baby steps. Baby steps.
就跟JP聊聊
Just talk to jp.
什么
What?
他可能同样喜欢你
He probably likes you, too.
但你不跟他说话你就永远都不知道结果
You'll just never know if you don't talk to him.
然后那些正看着你的人
And then everybody that's watching you,
他们会投票
they would just go on and vote.
谁想要看小维和JP调情
Who wants to see vee mackin' on jp?
上帝啊
Oh, my god!
你们够了
You guys!
想要看小维和JP调情的投“要”
All who wanna see vee macking on jp say, "Yes."
要
Yes!
- 要 要 - 你投"不要"吗
- Yes. Yes.- I assume, "No"?
- 弃权 - 感恩
- Abstain. - Thank you.
好了 你已经进入挑战游戏
All right. You've been dared.
你要接受挑战么 小维
Do you accept your dare, vee?
说 "要" 说 "要"
Say, "Yes." Say, "Yes."
重点是什么 我们就要毕业了 我
What's the point? We're graduating. I...
你只需要过去说个 嗨
All you have to do is say, "Hi."
我不想跟他打招呼
I don't want to say hello to him.
好吧
Fine.
我非常爱你 小维 但你只是个观众
I love you so much, vee. But you're a watcher.
所以看我为你这么做
So watch me do it for you.
别别别 小西小西 - 看着吧
No, no, no, Syd, Syd, Syd. Just watch.
别别别 小西 别
No, no, no! Syd, no.
耶 西德妮
Yeah! Sydney!
下次要不要把前面秀给我们看
Why don't you show us the front next time?
你先来 查克 我听说它很大
You first, Chuck. I hear it's really big.
大概就是平均水平
Guess it's average.
呃 嘿 JP
Uh... hey, jp.
啥事
What's up?
呃 我想知道 你现在有没有女朋友
Um... I was wondering. Do you have a girlfriend right now?
不要
No!
不是我问 是我朋友问
It's not for me. It's for a friend.
好吧 哪个朋友
Well, which friend?
呃
Um...
不...她不是我喜欢的类型
No, it's... She's not my type.
你根本不像你想象中那么性感
You're not nearly as hot as you think you are.
不 他是  你就是个人渣
Yes, he is! And you are a douchebag.
拜托 别走啊
No, don't go! Come on!
小维 小维
Vee! Vee!
让她去吧
Just let her go.
很糟啊 西德尼
Not cool, Sydney.
我只是想帮她
I'm just trying to help her.
BGM : SOAP – Melanie Martinez
别帮她了
Let's not help her.
她会想通的
She'll figure it out.
对不起 小维
你这么聪明  是他配不上你
别理西德尼 又不是所有人都是玩家
你好 欢迎来到玩命直播
Hello. Welcome to nerve.
已选择玩家
You have chosen player.
玩命直播是完全民主的
Nerve is a direct democracy.
你的冒险将由观众决定
Watchers decide your dares.
统计结束之后
The two players with the most watchers
观众最多的两位玩家
by the end of regulation
将会晋级最终决赛
will advance to the final round,
最终赢家将获得全部奖金
where the winner takes all.
观众可以随时观看
Watchers can watch from anywhere,
但我们鼓励看现场直播
but they are encouraged to film live.
所以不要太惊慌失措
So don't be alarmed.
三条规则
There are three rules.
第一 所有冒险必须在玩家的手机上进行录制
One, all dares must be filmed on the player's phone.
第二 只有两个方式淘汰玩家
Two, there are only two ways to be eliminated.
失败或退出
Fail or bail.
第三 告密者会受惩罚
Three, snitches get stitches.
感谢您为玩命直播保守秘密
Thank you for keeping nerve a secret.
玩家 祝你好运
Good luck, player.
指纹登陆
准备好你的第一
次胆量测试了吗
接受
玩命直播 纽约 玩家 档案: @小维_99
嘿 我是小维 我现在没有空...
Hey, this is vee, I'm not here right now...
小维 你得注册来看我
Vee! You have to sign up and watch me.
账户信息 请按一
For account information, press one.
电话或信用卡信息和支付
For phone or credit card information and payment...
- 汤米 - 嘿 我正停车
- Tommy. - Hey, I'm pulling up outside.
什么事那么急
What the hell's so urgent?
我们得去柱廊餐馆
We have to go to colonnade diner.
－我们只有15分钟 －为什么 发生什么了
- We have 15 minutes. - Why? What's going on?
我注册了玩命直播 我的第一个冒险就在那儿
I signed up for nerve and that's where my first dare is.
什么意思 你注册为玩家了吗
What do you mean? You signed up as a player?
天哪
Oh, man.
怎么 有那么难以置信吗
What? Is that so hard to believe?
你知道据说西雅图有孩子因为玩命直播死了吗
You know that some kid supposedly died in Seattle playing nerve?
哦 我才不信
Oh, I don't buy that.
如果有孩子死了 那游戏早就被叫停了
If kids were dying, the game would be shut down.
不 他们没法叫停它 服务器不止一台
No, they can't shut it down. There's not a single server.
什么意思
What does that mean?
每个人电脑注册后
Everybody that logs onto the game
都会变成新的服务器
becomes a new server.
因此这游戏根本没法叫停
So it's impossible to turn the game off.
你怎么那么了解这个游戏
How do you even know so much about this game?
你从来不玩的
You've never even played.
听着 我花很多时间上暗网的 好吗
Look, I spend a lot of time on the dark web, all right?
哦 花很多时间在暗网上
Oh, a lot of time on the dark web?
是吗 黑客男孩
Is that right, hacker boy?
是的 就是这样
Yes, that is right.
你知道吗 你只能接触到整个互联网的百分之十
You're only accessing 10% of the Internet, you know.
你为什么要这样 真的 这很危险
Why are you even doing this? Seriously, it's dangerous.
因为西德尼吗
Is it because of Sydney?
和她无关 我...
This is not about Sydney. I'm...
这真的不是你的风格
It's just not like you.
你说到重点了
That's the point.
亲吻一个陌生人五秒钟
和一位陌生人接吻五秒 陌生人吗
Kiss a stranger for five seconds? A stranger?
小维 我会给你一百美元
Vee, I'll give you $100.
接受
好的好的
Okay, okay.
你要和随便一个人接吻吗
You're just gonna kiss some random person?
他有女友了
Oh... He has a girlfriend.
嗨
Hi.
快点
就亲那个人好了
Just kiss that guy.
好 我要亲那个人了
Okay. I'm gonna kiss that guy.
就是我说的那个人
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
我要做了
Gonna do it.
或者那个人
Or that guy.
他在看书
He reads.
做决定吧 时间紧迫
Well, make a choice. Clock's ticking.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
我要亲那个人
I'm kissing that guy.
好 你先坐在这里
Okay, you sit here.
开始录像了就告诉我
Tell me when you're rolling, 'Kay?
好吧 现在 这是不可能任务了
'Okay, it's mission impossible now?
上吧
Just go.
《到灯塔去》 这是我最喜欢的书
To the lighthouse, that's my favorite book.
真的吗
Really?
快告诉我吧 他们最终到了灯塔吗
Please, tell me they get to the lighthouse in the end.
嗯...
Um...
不 别说
Actually, don't tell me.
呃...好吧 还是快点说吧
Uh... okay, just tell me real quick.
是 他们到了 但是...
Yeah, they do, but that's...
但那不是重点
That's not really what it's about.
那个灯塔象征了一些东西
The lighthouse means something
它对每一个角色都不同
different to each of the characters.
它基本上代表了
It basically represents
那些角色们生活中最渴望的东西
the thing they want most in life.
抱歉 我书呆子气又犯了 把你的故事全毁了
And I'm sorry that I'm totally geeking out and ruining the story.
没事 是我问的你
No, I was the one who asked.
呃...
Um...
一 二
One Mississippi, two Mississippi,
三 四 五
three Mississippi, four Mississippi, five Mississippi.
结束
Done.
好吧 好了 拜拜
Okay. Okay, bye.
任务达成
我简直不敢相信我居然成功了
I can't believe I just did that!
闭嘴 我的天 为什么我觉得很尴尬
Shut up! Oh. Gosh, why am I embarrassed?
你拍下来了吗
Did you get it?
嗯 那就像个迷你剧 而我把六集全录下来了
Yeah, it was a miniseries. I got all six episodes.
他去哪儿了
Where did he go?
我不知道
I have no clue.
小维 一百美元已汇入您账户
"Vee, $100 has been wired to your account."
我要去看看吗
Should I check?
仔细看看
Should totally check.
他在干嘛
What is he doing?
不知道
I have no clue.
BGM ：YOU GOT IT – Roy Orbison
他在给我唱歌
He's singing to me.
不 这是个冒险 是个冒险
No, it's a dare. It's a dare.
你做到了
You got it.
谢谢 干得漂亮
Thank you. Good job.
恭喜你通过了胆量测试
You won your dare. Congratulations.
你也是
Back at ya.
我那个真是太尴尬了
Mine was totally embarrassing,
但是 嘿 至少我有了一百美元啊
but, hey, at least I got 100 bucks, right?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我发誓我不知道会发生什么 你介意吗
I promise I didn't know what was comin'. You mind?
抱歉 我坐在这儿
Sorry, I'm sitting here.
他们刚刚要我坐在那个位置... 抱歉
They just told me to sit in that booth and... sorry.
嗯...有个小孩过来给了我那本书
Um... some kid came by and gave me that book.
到灯塔去 我最喜欢的书
To the lighthouse, yeah, my favorite.
是啊 它就在你的脸书主页
Exactly. Because it's on your Facebook page.
他们掌握关于你的所有信息 小维
They know all the information about you, vee.
你叫小维吗
Your name's vee?
维纳斯的简称
Short for Venus.
我喜欢
I like that.
呃 她的父母给她起了爱神的名字
Well, her parents, they named her after the goddess of love.
那是罗马神话里的
There's a Roman myth.
是啊 我想我妈想到的是别人
Yeah, I guess my mom was expecting somebody else.
这不清楚了  吻的不错
I dunno about that. That was some kiss.
我还要去玩游戏 晚安了
I got a game to play. But good night to you guys.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么了
What?
和他进城
显然 观众们希望看见我们在一起
Apparently, the watchers like us together.
我是说 我甚至没法去城里 好吗
I mean, you can't even go to the city, right?
你知道的 我不会去城里的
You know, I can't go to the city, yeah.
我都还没在玩呢 我只是挑战一下
I'm not even playing, I was just doing one dare.
你确定 那可是两百美元
You sure? It's 200 bucks.
呃 先生 她很确定
Uh... She's pretty sure, man.
他老爱对你指手画脚吗
He always tell you what to do?
不 不 他不这样的
No. No, he doesn't.
如果你改变心意了 我就在外面
I'm gonna be outside if you change your mind.
很高兴认识你 小维
It's nice to meet you, vee.
再见了 哥们
See ya, man.
他以为这些薯条是我们买的
He thought that those were our fries.
我挺想要200美元的
I could use 200 bucks.
小维 你不会去城里的
Vee, you're not going to the city.
你说了只挑战一次
You said one dare.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你知道吗 查尔斯 曼森也是个歌手
You know what? Charles manson was a singer.
我正祈祷你能来呢
I was hoping you'd come.
提醒下你 我不觉得我是个好同伴
I'm just warning you, I don't think I'd make a very good partner.
我胆子不大
I'm not the daredevil type.
事实上 你该和我的朋友西德尼组队
You should team up with my friend Sydney, actually.
她痴迷玩命直播
She's obsessed with playing nerve.
但观众们希望我们组队
But the watchers want me to team up with you.
如果我不舒服了 我就退出
The second I feel uncomfortable, I'm out.
很公平
That's fair.
好吧
Okay.
等等
Hold on.
BGM : ELECTRIC LOVE – BØRNS
我得去下卫生间
I just have to go to the bathroom.
天哪
Oh, my god.
不好意思 女士们 女士们
Excuse me, ladies? Ladies?
你要去哪儿
Hey, where are you going?
拜托 让我冲你放个屁 拜托
Please, let me fart on you. Please!
天哪 天哪
Oh, my god, oh, my god!
天哪
Oh, my god.
晋级好快 我知道
It's going up so fast! I know.
你最爱的玩家是谁
Who's your favorite player?
我是说 我本来要说你的 但是...
Well, I mean, I was gonna say you, but...
现在我无法抉择了
Now I don't know.
那是小维吗
Is that vee?
是啊 她在玩玩命直播 而且 她有不少观众了
Yeah, she's playing nerve and she has, like, a lot of watchers.
天哪 妹子
Oh, my god, girl!
嘿 试试尖叫吧
Hey, try screaming.
不 叫出来吧 叫出声
No. Just do it. Let it out!
就是这样
There you go.
很好 就是这样
All right, this is it.
我要和你一起进去吗
Am I supposed to come in with you?
呃...
Uh...
观众没说这个
Doesn't say anything about that.
谢谢你载我一程
Well, thank you for the lift.
你没事吧
You gonna be okay?
恩恩 不 我...
Yeah, yeah, no, I'm...
我有点累 所以我得...
I'm tired, so I'm probably just gonna
我马上就回家了
make my way back home.
呃
Um...
这一路很有趣
This was fun.
是的
Yeah.
我要去…你知道的
I just gotta... you know.
嗯嗯
Okay.
穿上这件裙子
拒绝
接受
你又多走了三步
You got three more steps.
如果你坚持做训练
If you keep up the exercises,
你肯定会变得很强壮
you're gonna get really strong on that.
太棒了
Excellent.
谢谢你 小姐
Thanks, miss.
有人给小维打了钱
Somebody's sending vee money.
这是白人才有的问题
White people problems.
她在干什么
What is she doing?
这是你的收据
And you have your receipt.
感谢您在波道夫购物
So thank you so much for shopping at Bergdorf's.
- 祝您今天愉快  - 呃 抱歉 打扰了
- You have a wonderful day. - Excuse me. Um... sorry.
你能告诉我在哪儿可以找到这条裙子吗
Do you know where I can find this dress?
你妈妈打电话来了
Your mom's calling.
该死
Shit!
这条裙子很贵
That's very expensive.
高级定制 在四层楼
Couture. Fourth floor.
谢谢
Thanks.
请不要脱模特身上的衣服
Please, don't undress the mannequin.
抱歉
Sorry.
您是想试试这件吗
Would you like to try this on?
呃 嗯
Mmm-hmm.
我来看看能不能找到你的尺码
Let me see if I have it in your size.
谢谢你
Thank you.
麻烦能快一点吗
If you could hurry up,
我派对要迟到了
I'm a little bit late for a party.
你真可爱
Cute.
好了 请到这边来
Okay. Right this way.
如果您还需要别的 尽管找我
If you need anything else, just let me know.
- 好的 谢谢 - 喔 好吧
- Okay, thank you. - Oh. All right.
脱光吧宝贝!
这可能是她最好的角度了
同楼上
好瘦啊
素食主义者吧
#$100 打个赌她能不能拉上拉链
#我赌  用户@W10534
$2#我赌她可以反手拉上
她屁股上是个熊猫么
是啊这孩子才五岁吧
我总算有点兴趣看看这妹纸了
我更想看她的性转兄弟
她好假啊
她跟个十岁的小男孩似的
等会  我看不到她了
好了 我穿好了
Okay. Dressed.
嘿
Hello?
有什么问题吗
Everything okay?
没事儿 谢谢
Everything is great, thank you.
嘿 可以告诉我你的邮件吗 我的意思是你的
Hey. What's your email number? I mean your...
你的联系方式
What's your info?
什么 那种过时的东西
Oh, this? This old thing?
小维
Vee!
哦
Oh.
嗨
Hey.
嘿
Hi.
你 你看上去美极了
You, uh... You look very pretty.
谢谢 你也是
Thanks. So do you.
我的意思是你看上去很性感 很英俊 很…
I mean you look, you know, hot, or handsome or...
你知道我们现在应该做什么吗
Do you know what we're supposed to do now?
观众们想看我
The watchers would like me
帮你完成你的全套装扮 小姐
to complete your ensemble, mademoiselle.
没有 有这个选项吗
Neither. Is that an option?
观看你最爱的玩家
每24小时只需$19.99
同意
好吧  来看看我们的新手
All right, how 'bout my firstborn son, too? Yeah?
欢迎  观看
汤米 曼库索
你的匿名ID是
搜索玩家:
维纳斯 德尔莫尼科
你在干什么 小维
What are you doing, vee?
先生 这些多少钱
How much are they, sir?
一共900块钱 女士
That'll be $900, madam.
如果是这个价格的话 我要两双
Oh, in that case, I'll take two.
一双在城里穿 一双在汉普顿穿
One for the city and one for the Hamptons.
很棒的选择 小姐
Excellent choice, mademoiselle.
我现在就给您包起来
I'll wrap them up for you right away.
任务达成
我们楼下见
Um, I'll see ya downstairs?
行
Uh... yeah, sure.
好的
Okay. All right.
怎么回事
What?
哦 打扰了 小姐
Oh, excuse me, miss!
请问你动过我里面的衣服吗
Did you move my clothes in there?
当然没有
Of course not.
这不可能
This is not happening.
小维
Vee?
伊恩
Ian.
嗨
Hey.
你是不是拿了我的东西 我的钱包和衣服
Did you take my stuff? I mean, my wallet, my clothes.
所有的东西都没了
Everything's gone.
我的东西也没了
No, my stuff is gone, too.
离开商店
拒绝
接受
不
No.
-好吧 -不不
-Okay, um... -No. No.
快点 我们赶紧跑
Come on, we have to make a run for it.
快点 快走 我不想偷东西
Come on, let's go. I am not shoplifting!
我们没有选择 快走吧
We don't have a choice. Come on!
好吧 严格意义上来说
Okay, technically,
它只是叫我们必须离开这家店吧
it just says we have to leave the store.
对不对
Right?
BGM : RIDE – Lowell featuring Icona Pop
快走
Let's go.
快点 快点 走啊
Come on, come on! Let's go!
呃
Mmm...
嗯…
Um...
抱歉 伙计 让我们过去一下 抱歉
Sorry, buddy, we need to come through. Sorry.
请让一下 请让一下
Excuse me! Excuse me!
够了 够了 快走 快点 快点
That's enough, that's enough. Let's go, come on, come on.
哇喔 哇喔 嘿 嘿 停下停下停下
Whoa, whoa, hey, stop, stop, stop!
求你告诉我这些是我们的衣服
Please tell me these are our clothes!
差不多是
They kind of are.
这些是被偷来的
Are these stolen?
有收据
Receipt.
我们可以穿这些衣服了
We get to keep 'em?
都是你的
All yours.
好吧
All right.
嘿我能买单吗
Hey, can I get the check?
谁付的钱
Who paid for these?
可能是某个观众拿老爸的信用卡买的吧
Probably one of the watchers with daddy's credit card.
- 什么 - 你看
- What? - Look!
你哼的是武当派的歌吗
I'm sorry, was that a wu-tang reference?
史塔顿岛 代表作
Staten island, represent!
好吧
Okay.
去圣马克 十分钟为限
Saint Mark's, 10 minutes?
你好
Hello.
汤米 小维以为自己在干什么
Tommy, what does Vee think she's doing?
你长这么大停过车吗你
Have you ever parked a car in your life?
我搞的定
I got this, girl.
我怎么知道 西德
I have no idea, Syd.
你问我干什么 我又不是她男朋友
Why are you asking me? I'm not her boyfriend.
那跟她组队骑摩托车的那个人是谁
Well, who's this biker she's teamed up with?
我不知道 她把我甩下了
I have no clue. She just ditched me.
看上去她是在做她觉得最有益的事
She's doing what she apparently thinks is best for herself.
那到底是什么事
Yeah, and what exactly is that?
西德尼 西德
Sydney! Syd!
小维上了榜单前十
Vee is in the top 10.
什么
What?
她在前十名了
She's in the top 10.
汤米 小维在前十名了
Tommy, Vee is in the top 10?
-是的 我知道 -这怎么可能
-Yeah, I know. -How is that even possible?
她有多少观众
How many watchers does she have?
大约4471
Um... like 4,471.
我有多少
How many do I have?
Uh... 6,806.
好吧 我还是比她多得多
Oh, okay, I have a lot more.
汤米 我真的不觉得小维能处理好这件事
Tommy, I really don't think that vee can handle this.
我真的很担心她
I'm actually really worried about her.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
所以快滚来派对帮我 好吗
So get your ass to this party and help me, okay?
好的好的 我在路上了
Yeah, yeah, I'm on my way.
BGM : HURRICANE (ARTY REMIX) – Halsey
圣马可街
如果我放弃会怎样
What happens if I bail?
你会失去你现在拿到的一切
You'd lose everything you've already made.
我妈妈会杀了我的
My mom would kill me.
你想怎么做呢
What do you wanna do?
让伊恩给你选纹身
拒绝
接受
好吧 求你不要选什么喷火或者刀子
Okay, just please no fire-breathing dragons or knives.
－也不要小丑 －好的
－No clowns. －Okay.
不要蛇 不要骷髅
No snakes, no skeletons.
黑豹和龙卷风呢
What about panthers and tornados?
－不 －不吗
－No! －No?
－不要 －好吧
－No! －Okay.
哇哦 这个如何
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What about this?
我爸爸的纹身
Just a tattoo of my dad.
他简直酷毙了 非常正直 长的又帅
He's gorgeous, honestly. He's a nice-looking guy.
哈 好吧 我有个更好的主意 就是这样 就是这样
Ah... okay. I got a better idea. Here we go. Here we go.
你要自己画一个 不
You're gonna draw it? No!
- 小维 别出声 我得专心 - 让我看看
- Vee, quiet. I gotta concentrate! - No! Let me see.
后退
Back off.
好吧
'Kay.
你能纹这个吗 但是要稍微好看点儿
Can you do something like this, but less shitty?
当然可以
Yes!
是吗
Yeah?
对 我笑是因为它很赞
Right. I'm laughing 'cause it's good.
你们别这样好吗
You guys, come on!
嘿 你得相信我们 信任是一切的基础
Hey, you have to trust us. That's the whole thing.
你得相信我
Gotta trust me.
和这位脏胡须老哥
And dirt beard.
噢 噢 好了 好了
Ow! Ow! Okay. Okay.
好了 你可以停下了
Okay, you can stop.
我觉得你可以停下了 我觉得我们这样很好 可以了
I think you can stop. I think we're good. We're good.
胆量测试要求说只需要大于一个硬币就好了
The dare said it just had to be bigger than a quarter.
这绝对比硬币大了
This definitely feels bigger than a quarter.
你表现得很棒 就快成功了
You're doin' great. It's almost done.
好吧 我觉得不管到哪里了 都可以停下了
Okay, no, I think wherever we're at, we can just stop.
噢 噢 噢
Ow, ow, ow...
慢点 我正在写“爸爸”的最后一笔
Hold on, I'm just doing the "Y" In "Daddy."
什么
What?
他在开玩笑 别听他的啦
He's kidding. Don't listen to him.
我真的很不喜欢这个声音 太讨厌了
I really don't like that noise. At all.
BGM :  C.R.E.A.M. – Wu-Tang Clan
噢
Ow!
我的天
Oh, my god.
让金牙摇滚起来
Rockin' that gold tooth.
停下
Stop!
好的好的 噢
Okay, okay. Ow!
Wu-tang粉丝 哈
Wu-tang fan, huh?
我哥哥之前整天他们的歌
My brother used to listen to them all the time.
是吗 你还有个哥哥
Oh, yeah? You have a brother?
曾经有过
Had a brother.
他上大学没多久就去世了
He died right before starting college.
我很抱歉 这是多久之前的事
I'm sorry. How long ago was that?
两年前
Two years ago.
他才十八岁
He was 18.
这个七月 我就要比他大了
This July, I'll be older than him.
比我的 大哥哥大
Older than my older brother.
噢 噢
Ow, ow...
嘿 看着我 注意力放在我这
Hey, hey. Come on. Stay with me. Stay with me.
他只是那群无所畏惧的人中的一位
He was just one of those people that wasn't afraid of anything.
他总是说"是的"
He always said, "Yes."
他会放声大笑
He would laugh so hard
如果他现在看到我纹身了
if he saw me getting a tattoo right now.
嘭 我完工了
Boom! I am done.
去镜子那看看 庆祝我的工作成果
Go to that mirror. Celebrate my work.
来嘛
Come on.
你想看看吗 是的 是的 是的
Do I want to see? Yes, yes, yes.
- 嘿 - 吃晚饭 少年绝地武士
- Hey. - 'Sup, young jedi?
对 啊哈哈 我们在俱乐部这边很想你
Yeah, ha-ha. Hey. Yo, we miss you down here at the club.
额 你在看 玩命直播 对吗
Um... you're watching nerve, right?
是的 老兄 我们都在看
Yeah, man, we all are.
好的 我在调查这个叫伊恩的家伙更多的底细
All right, I'm trying to find out more about this Ian guy.
伊恩 我朋友
Ian, my dude.
老兄 他调戏在你妹子 小维 对吗
Man, he playin' wit' your little girlfriend vee, right?
也可能是你 跟你耍
Could be you, but you're playin'.
好吧 是的 这才是问题所在
All right, yes. That's the problem, though.
我在看他的资料
But I'm looking at his profile
但是他什么都没有
and there's just nothing on the guy.
听着 小婊砸 你试过谷歌吗
Look, bitch, you tried Google?
是的 我试过谷歌
Yeah, I tried Google.
看来他就是个幽灵
Guess he's a ghost, then.
听着 我需要阿鲁巴的通行票
Look, I need a ticket to Aruba.
- 什么 不 - 是的 就这样
- Uh... what? No. - Yes, come on!
不可以 你根本没准备
No way. You're not ready for that shit.
是 我知道 你会坏了我的信誉
Yes, I know. You're gonna mess up my rating.
我不会坏你的信誉
I'm not gonna mess up your rating.
我又不是买枪支什么的 老兄 拜托
I'm not gonna buy guns or something, man. Come on.
汤米 不 没可能
Tommy, no. Not happening.
我 听着 我只是担心我的朋友 求你了
I'm... look, I'm just worried about my friend. Please.
拜托
Come on.
好吧 我给你发个密码
All right, I'll send you a passkey.
好的 谢谢
All right. Thank you.
灯塔 我喜欢 谢谢你
A lighthouse? I love it. Thank you.
有个智者曾经说过
Well, a very wise person once said...
就是今天早些时候说的
And this was earlier today.
他们说 灯塔象征着
They said that the lighthouse represents
你最想要的东西
the thing that you want the most.
所以 不管那是什么 我希望你得到他
So, whatever that is, I hope you get it.
她现在有多少粉丝了
How many followers does she have now?
我是说 坦白地说 你确实告诉她去冒险了
I mean, to be fair, you did tell her to take a risk.
我不是这意思 丽芙
This isn't what I meant, Liv.
这太扯了
This is ridiculous.
西德尼
Sydney!
好吧 现在他们问我是否相信你 我能吗
Okay. Now they're asking if I can trust you. Can I?
你相信维么？
我给你选个非常完美的纹身
I have the perfect tattoo picked out for you.
等下 等下 等下
Wait, wait, wait.
不要 好吧 这不是纹身冒险
No, okay, it's not a tattoo dare.
这是什么
What is it?
只是说"去25号公园"
Just says, "Go to park and 25th."
给你...
别干坏事  蠢货
谢谢 我欠你份人情
~ 一个脑洞大开的封闭社区 ~
密匙
授权
哦 上帝 我爱互联网
Oh, god, I love the Internet.
什么
What?
伊恩 玩命直播 胆量测试 摩托车
我为玩命直播而活 今年尤甚
今年好多玩家啊
好多钱
光纽约就好多
这玩意儿越搞越大了
这货有赢得潜力
偷的车
我不敢相信他居然又开始玩了
...西雅图都出事了
去年太狂热了
什么
What?
伊恩之前玩过
Ian's played before?
没必要这么做 拍下来就好
Don't have to do this. Just shoot it!
嘿 这里是小维 我现在不在 有事请留言
Hey, it's vee. I'm not here right now, so leave a message.
这就出发
Here we go.
能达到每小时60英里 就这样
Get to 60 miles per hour. That's it.
好的
Okay.
好吧 来了个简单的 那我们做这个
All right. Easy one. All right, let's do this.
哦
Oh!
那上面刚才说什么
What did that just say?
蒙眼驾驶 60英里/小时
蒙眼 骑摩托
Blindfolded? On the motorcycle?
是的
Yeah.
那你自己玩吧
You're on your own with that one.
等等 我自己玩不来
Wait, wait. I can't do this alone.
来嘛 我需要你帮我导航
Come on, I need you to help me navigate.
我才不干这事呢
There is no way in hell I'm doing that.
抱歉 我退出
I'm sorry, I'm out.
今晚谢谢你 我是说…
Thank you for tonight. I mean...
玩得也开心 还有新裙子 但是我…
I had a lot of fun. Got a new dress. But I...
我不玩了
I'm good.
留下 让我们看看会发生什么
Stay. Let's see what else happens.
哟 怎么了 伙计 维纳斯 爱死你们了
Yo! What's up, guys? Venus, love your work.
能帮我拿着这个吗
Would you hold that for me?
拿好
Hold it up.
很好
Great.
还有伊恩 决赛见
And, Ian, see you in the finals.
那家伙是谁
Who was that guy?
我不知道 另一个玩家吧
I don't know. Just another player.
小维 走吧 跟我一起来
Vee, come on, do this with me.
求你了 我需要你
Please, I need you.
听着 你肯定会掌控好的
Look, you'd be in control.
说"好"啊 说"好"吧
Say, "Yes." Just say, "Yes."
下一个是谁 谁想挑战冠军 丽芙
Who got next? Who wanna challenge the champ? Liv?
- 不是吧 - 嘿 丽芙 来吧
- No way. - Hey, Liv, come on!
西德尼
Sydney!
西德 西德尼
Syd... Sydney!
怎么了
What?
我的天哪 你肯定不敢相信
Oh, my god, you're not gonna believe this.
蒙眼驾驶 60英里/小时
什么 在逗我吗
What? Are you kidding me?
准备好了吗
You ready?
是的
Yeah.
查克 你看这个了吗
Chuck, you seein' this?
好吧 记住 你是我的眼
All right, remember, you're my eyes.
好的
Okay.
绿灯了
Green.
坐稳
Hold on.
- 你还好吗  - 还好
- You okay? - Yeah.
要时刻留神
Just keep your eyes open.
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
嘿 我知道你害怕 但你得跟我交流 小维
Hey, I know you're scared, but you gotta talk to me, vee.
好吧等等 不不不
Okay, wait, no, no, no!
我能行 小维
You got this, vee.
怎么回事 我们还好吗 右边有出租车
What's goin' on? Are we good? Taxi to the right.
右边 右边 不
Right! Right! No!
你头盔上有张贴纸
You have a sticker on your helmet!
谢谢 你偏右了 你得往左
Thank you! You're leaning right. You need to go left.
- 左边 左边 - 喔 抱歉
- Left, left! - Whoa, sorry!
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
- 抱歉 抱歉 抱歉 - 现在可以吗
- Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! - We good?
可以 可以 太左了 往右 往右
Okay, okay! Too far left. Right! Right!
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
好的 我觉得默契了 现在可以吗
Okay, I think that worked. Yeah? Are we good?
现在 可以了
Actually, yes.
好的 就这样 保持住
Okay, all right, just keep doin' that.
就测斜吗
Just lean?
是的 测斜 往左或往右 你能行的
Yes, lean. Left or right. You are in control.
就这样
That's good.
她不可能做到的
No way she's doing this.
快点
Faster.
很好 你做的很棒
This is good. You're doin' great!
好的 加速
Okay, speed up.
遵命 长官
Yes, ma'am.
好的
Okay.
到30码了 还有一半
We hit 30. We're halfway there.
好的 下一个红绿灯是…
Okay, the next light is...
绿灯
Green!
下一个红绿灯是…绿灯
The next light's... green!
很好 很好 没错 你做到了
Good, good, all right, you got this.
好的 下一个红绿灯是
Okay, the next light is...
快点 跟住我思路 怎么回事
Come on, stay with me. What's goin' on?
下一个是绿灯 快点
Next light is green! Faster!
不不不不
No! No, no, no!
绿灯
Green!
还有多少时间 小维
We're doin' this, vee!
60秒
Sixty seconds.
- 现在有障碍吗 - 目前没有
- Are we clear now? - Still clear.
出租车 出租车
Taxi! Taxi!
哦 上帝
Oh, god.
带他回家 小维 带他回家 小维
Take it home, vee! Take it home, vee!
没错 小维
Yeah, vee!
- 检查时间 - 15秒
- Time check. - Fifteen seconds.
- 速度 - 45 46
- Speed? - Forty-five,Forty-six
Forty-seven
伊恩 我们爱你
Ian, we love you!
我也爱你
Love you, too!
行了 我们走
All right, let's go!
Fifty-seven,
58 59
Fifty-eight,Fifty-nine
Sixty
我们做到了
We did it!
卧槽 小心
Oh, shit! Look out!
坐稳了 天哪 哦我的天 小心
Hold on! God, oh, my god! Look out!
耶耶耶
Yeah!
最刺激的冒险 小维是第一
Best dare ever! Vee is number one!
哦我的天
Oh, my god.
我是我做过最疯狂的事情 你太不可思议了
That was the craziest thing I've ever done. You were incredible.
我甚至不敢相信我们做到了
I can't even believe we did that.
她亲了他
She kissed him!
哦 小维 拿下他 姑娘
Oh, vee! Get him, girl!
哦耶
Oh, yeah!
你饿了吗
You hungry at all?
-披萨 - 披萨
- Pizza? - Pizza...
我发誓 我刚想说 披萨
I swear, I was gonna say, "Pizza."
嘿 观众们
Hey, watchers.
好的 听着
Okay, listen,
你我都清楚 我也该入围的
you and I both know that I should be in that box.
所以拜托了 别拘束 好吗
So please, stop holding back. Okay?
你们不用害怕 因为我就不害怕
You guys don't need to be afraid, because I'm not afraid.
所以给我个真正的挑战
So just give me a real dare.
怎么了 小西宝贝
What's up, Syd baby?
你来这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
你是个好玩家
You're a good player.
你有很多观众 我有很多观众
You've got a lot of watchers. I got a lot of watchers.
也许我们可以合作
Maybe we could team up.
我不需要合作
I don't need a partner.
看你朋友小维 好像挺有用的
Seems to work for your friend vee.
怎么了 小西 你还好吗
What up, Syd? You all right?
没事 我们在聊天
Yeah. We're just talking.
哟 疯狂麦克斯 你自己出去吧 伙计
Yo, mad Max, why don't you show yourself out, man?
打电话
Call me.
吓唬你
Break down!
队长
Captain.
派对继续啊 老兄
Party on, man.
嘿 南希
Hey, Nancy.
汤米 听着 我有个小问题
Tommy, listen, I have a quick question.
我怎么才能知道我是不是被黑了
How would I know if I'm being hacked?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
被骇了 有人在小维的名义下
Hacked. Somebody's been depositing money
给我的账户打钱
into my account under vee's name.
那听上去可不像黑客
That doesn't sound like a hack.
黑客要黑你的话
Normally, they would take money out
应该是取走你的钱吧
if they were hacking you.
托马斯 你有什么瞒着我吗
Thomas, what are you not telling me?
哦...那个...小维找了份工作
Oh! It must... it might be... Vee got a job.
什么 工作
What? A job?
对 差不多
Yeah, that's probably it.
他在网上找了个扑克牌类的工作
She did an online poker thing.
嗯
Okay.
- 而且她很擅长 - 那合法吗
- And she's really great at it. - Is it legal?
嗯 合法的 她做得不错
Yeah, it's legal. And she's doing great,
收入合法 都可以给你打钱
as you can tell with the deposits.
那个啥 我得挂了
But anyway, I gotta go.
我最近在写关于摩托安全的论文
I'm writing a paper right now on motorcycle safety.
- 我得继续写... - 那让小维给我回电话啊
- I'm gonna get goin', but... - Well, tell her to call me.
- 拜 - 拜
- Bye. - Bye.
BGM ：DOWN LOW – Alex Winston
想玩一会吗
Wanna take a ride?
这又是个冒险吗
Is this a dare?
并不是 我是说玩旋转木马
Mmm-mmm. It's a carousel.
你为什么要玩玩命直播呢
So, why are you playing nerve?
赢钱养家糊口
Trying to help out my family.
发生了一些事情 我希望能有些转变
Some things happened that I wish turned out differently.
什么事情
Like what?
就是些...我得处理的一些事
This is just kinda something I need to do.
就是这样...
So...
狗仔队来了
We got some paparazzi.
快躲
Hide.
谁的电话呀
What? Who is it?
接受
拒绝
是西德尼呀
So that's Sydney.
- 快接 快接 - 你要接吗
- Pick up, pick up. - You gonna get it?
现在不想理她
I don't wanna deal with her right now.
矮油
Ouch!
你们怎么了
What's goin' on?
她最近挺犯贱
She's just been a lot recently.
管她呢 你肯定不想听的
But whatever, you don't wanna talk about that.
你想谈的话 我就乐意听
If you wanna talk about it, I'm here. Happy to listen.
我只是厌倦了 不想给她当背景了
I'm just tired of being her sidekick all the time.
有趣 其实你不像任何人的背景呀
It's funny. You don't seem like anyone's sidekick.
我能再看看她的照片吗
Can I see that picture again?
哦 嗯...
Oh, uh...
好啊
Sure.
哇
Wow.
没错 小伙子们都迷死她了
Yeah. Guys go crazy for her.
不 我是说照片拍得好
No, I mean the picture itself. It's really good.
谢了 那是我拍的
Thanks, I took it.
是吗 真有双发现美的眼睛
Yeah? You have a good eye.
我...想象不出来你你能跟她这样的在一起
I just... I can't picture you hangin' out with someone like this.
什么意思
What do you mean?
不知道 她看上去有点...
I don't know. She looks kind of...
不安全 对吧
Insecure. Is that mean?
- 她相当不安全  -嗯
- She is totally insecure. - Yeah?
而且她让我看起来像是那个不安全的
She makes it seem like I'm the one who's insecure.
其实就是她
But really it's her.
心累
It's exhausting.
是啊
I'm sure.
这次派对
She's at this party.
她肯定又得喝得烂醉 要我去搀着
Most likely drunk and needs me to hold her hair back.
不想理她了
I'm just over it.
我是说 她父母也是
I mean, so are her parents.
时不时就出门
They're constantly out of town,
她就把房门向别人敞开
so she has this revolving door of guys over.
其实挺惨呢
It's sad, actually.
嘿 那个派对
Hey, that party.
我们是不是该去看看
Should we maybe go check it out?
什么
What?
我为什么会想去呢
Why would I wanna go to that party?
或许秀一秀你的新纹身
Maybe show off your new tattoo?
让西德尼知道你不是她认为的那样
Show Sydney that you're not the person she thinks you are?
BGM : GIVE ME MORE – Grandtheft
@Syd_Baby_XO  想好好来个大冒险...我们给她出一个
让她给我打电话,我会给她出个好的
讲真  我们该出个什么???
来个吓人的
没错  好好吓吓她
让她去高处怎么样
嘿 小心 注意 借过一下
Yo, watch out! Heads up. Comin' through.
小心
Yo, watch out.
好的 我能行 好的
Okay. I got this. Okay.
上啊 西德尼
Go, Sydney!
你比这强多了
You're better than this.
开始吧 转个身就好
Come on, just turn around.
加油 小西 你能行
Come on, Syd, you got this.
加油啊小西 接受挑战就得完成它
Come on, Syd, you started it, you gotta finish it.
上吧 没问题 没问题
Come on, you got it. You got it!
好吧
Okay.
深呼吸
Just take a deep breath.
深呼吸 西德尼
Just take a deep breath, Sydney.
快来看 要开始啦
Get in here! She's gonna do it!
妹子上啊
Go, girl!
强无敌
You got this. Okay.
- 开始了 加油 - 出发了
- There you go. Come on. - Yeah, there you go!
上吧上吧
There you go.
快去把丽芙叫来
Somebody, go get Liv!
哦 天哪
Oh, my god.
别停 小西 集中注意 没问题的
Come on, Syd. Focus. You got this.
丽芙 丽芙
Liv! Liv!
丽芙 快来 快来
Liv, Liv, Liv, come, come, come.
借过 借过
Excuse me, excuse me.
老天啊
Oh, my god. Syd!
当心 当心 小茜
Be careful. Be careful, Syd.
天啊 你在干什么
What are you doing? Oh, my god!
你用不着这样啊 回来
Come on, Syd, you don't have to do this. Come back.
闭嘴
Shut up!
西德尼 快回来
Sydney, come back.
天啊 西德尼
Oh, my god, Sydney!
很强 继续走
Yeah! There you go.
厉害了我的姐
Right here. Come on.
用不着这样啊
You don't have to do it.
不着急 小茜 别往下看
Take your time, Syd. Don't look down.
不就是个破游戏吗
It's just a stupid game!
可以的 很强
Come on, we're right here.
你随时可以回来 小西
You could always turn back, Syd.
快帮她一把 不行 必须直播
Jp, grab her. Come on, you gotta film.
茜德尼 不直播就不算数了
Sydney, it's not gonna count unless you film it.
别管手机了
Don't worry about the phone.
必须直播 必须...
She has to film it! She can't...
不直播就不算成功 她必须直播
It doesn't count unless she films it. She has to film it.
放弃吧 回来吧
不行 必须直播
Just bail. Just come back.
She has to film it. No, but she has to film it.
- 闭嘴 查克 - 哦 神啊 老天啊
Shut up, Chuck! Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
简直疯了
This is crazy.
行了 快 别往下看
All right, there you go. Don't look down.
不行 天哪 做不到啊
I can't! Oh, my god, I can't, I can't!
西德尼 快起来
Sydney, you gotta get up.
- 快点啊 - 别吼我
- You gotta do something. - Stop yelling at me!
- 别吼 你帮倒忙呢 - 查克 闭嘴
- Stop! You're not helping. - Chuck, shut up!
闭嘴 她没问题的
Shut up, she's got it.
她必须做完
She has to get it done!
别说了
Shut up!
小茜 这样太慢了 你得站起来走
Syd, it's gonna take too long, you gotta stand, you gotta walk.
别别别 别站啊茜德尼
No, don't stand, Sydney.
闭嘴 闭嘴 查克
Shut up! Shut up, Chuck!
你听见了 查克 快别说了
You heard her, Chuck, shut up.
她必须完成挑战
She's gotta get it done.
不站起来走就来不及了
She's not gonna get here in time unless you get up and walk.
快站起来
You have to walk.
别听他的 小西 你可以的
必须站起来 耽误太多时间了
Don't listen to him, Syd, you got it.
She has to! She's wasting time!
你们都给我闭嘴
Shut up, both of you!
别怕 加油 小西 没问题的
You got it. Come on, Syd, you got this.
不行了 不行 不行
I can't, I can't, I can't.
我放弃 放弃了
I bail, I bail, I bail.
你出局了
放弃挑战
You bail.
你失败了
挑战失败
You fail.
你失败了
挑战失败
You fail.
这太蠢了
This is so dumb.
快偷 抓住
Come here! Hold on!
挑战失败
You fail.
你失败了
滚回来
Get over here!
天啊
Oh, my god.
任务达成
你是第一名
BGM : CRIME CUTZ – Holy Ghost!!
轻轻关上门
关爱老年人
哇 快看看这俩
Oh! Look at these guys!
小维
Vee!
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi!
天呐 你们俩现在都成网红了
Oh, my gosh. You guys are so famous right now.
啊哦 等等让小西来看看你们
Uh-oh! Wait until Syd sees you.
她现在在哪呢
But where is she?
哦 你们不知道
Oh, you guys don't know?
她挑战横跨悬空梯子 刚刚放弃
Yeah, she tried to walk across that ladder and just bailed.
那她就游戏结束了
So she's outta the game?
嘿 喝一杯吧
Hey, let's get a drink.
对 弱爆了
Yeah. It wasn't pretty.
你们看到西德尼了吗
Have you seen Sydney?
在这么 小西
In there. Syd?
哦 别这么看我 小维 你都没怎么跟他聊过
Oh, come on, vee, you never even spoke to him.
没关系 没什么大不了
It's fine. Certainly, no surprise.
对 我知道没什么大不了
Yeah, I know it's not a surprise.
你知道是什么问题吗
You know what's not fine, though?
老娘今晚差点死了 小维 却找不到你
I almost died tonight, vee, and you were nowhere to be found.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你说我要过好我的人生
When you said I should live my life,
你意思是在你的影子下过吗
did you mean I should live my life in your shadow?
我是想帮你 小维
I was just trying to help you, vee,
因为你是我认识的最压抑的人
because you're the most repressed person that I know.
就因为这个你才和我交朋友吧
Well, isn't that why you keep me around?
因为我不告诉你真相
Because I never tell you the truth?
对啊
Yeah.
我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
我猜你不告诉我真相
I guess you don't tell me the truth.
是因为你从不告诉我我有多么的"不安全"
Because you never told me about how insecure I am.
我怎样"向别人敞开房门"
Or about how I just have a revolving door of guys all the time.
你从不跟我说 但今晚你却跟所有人都说了
You never tell me that, but you've told everyone that tonight.
所以 小维 快让我们看看这一下午
So please, vee, go right ahead and show us all
你能有多激情闪耀
what a fiery little spark plug you've become since lunch.
走吧
Let's go.
开火了哟
Shots fired.
别就这么一走了之 小维 醒醒吧
Don't walk away from me. Vee! Wake up!
这只是个游戏
This is a game.
你真的以为他这样的人
Do you really think that someone like him
最后会跟你走到一起吗
is actually gonna be with you when this is all done?
嘿 你才不了解我呢
Hey, you don't know me.
哦 抱歉哦 你现在真喜欢上她了
Oh, I'm sorry. You really like her now?
是的 我喜欢她
Yeah, I do.
对 我就是喜欢她
行了 小西 你喝多了
All right, come on, Syd, you're just drunk.
行了 西德 你已经醉了
汤米 该忘了她了
Tommy, it is time to get over her!
汤米 是时候摆脱她了
多明显呀 人家档次高了
Clearly, she has traded up!
你为什么要这么贱呢
Why do you have to be such a bitch?
听听
Look at that!
小维终于把心里话说出来了
Little vee finally speaking her mind.
得了吧 你就不要背着那些包袱了
Come on! Unburden yourself!
你知道为什么我们两个是做好的朋友么
Do you know why we're best friends?
一直都是我在替你忙前忙后
I do whatever you want all the time.
不 小维
No, vee, we're friends
因为我很有趣 而你 无聊的要命
because I'm fun and you're boring.
你身上唯一还算有意思的地方就是你哥哥
The only fun thing about you was your brother.
你以为是怎么回事
What is it you think?
你以为那些玩命直播
That playing nerve is just gonna
能够奇迹般的改变你么
magically make you a different person?
人生才不是那样 你永远都成不了玩家
That's not how life works. You'll never be a player.
你说的对
You're right.
我知道 你有多享受生活在这样的时刻 小西
I know how much you love living in the moment, Syd.
记住这一刻吧
Well, remember this moment.
你就像高中里的那些自大的女孩子一样
Because you're one of those girls who peaks in high school.
当有一天 你醒来的时候 就发现自己还生活在斯塔顿岛
And when you wake up one day, still living in staten island,
睡的还是那一群人
still screwing the same guys,
搞不清生活怎么成了这副样子
wondering what the hell happened to your life.
以后你要是还想关注我在哪的话
If you wanna know where I am from now on,
你就登陆账号去看我吧
sign up and watch me.
等等 小维 你要干什么
Wait, vee, what are you doing?
嘿 小维 你不必这样做的
Hey, vee, you don't need to do this.
看着我 算了吧 咱们走吧 退出吧
Look at me. Come on. Let's just go, let's bail, all right?
你有什么要证明的
What do you have to prove?
得了吧 小维 我们走
Come on, please. Let's go.
来吧 小维 你搞的定  拜托了
Come on, you got it, vee, please!
- 来吧 妹子 - 小维
- Go, girl! - Vee!
天呐 小维
Oh, my god. Vee!
哇
Whoa!
你做的到 小维
You got it, vee!
任务达成
完成西德尼的胆量测试
你现在是第一名
小维 你就是这样一步步变成第一的
That's how you get into first, vee!
这糟透了
That was messed up.
我现在没空管这个 我得走了
I can't deal with this right now. I'm gonna go.
小维 你知道他以前也是玩玩命直播的么
Vee, did you know that he's played nerve before?
什么
What?
他的挑战就是带你来这
Yeah, it was his dare to get you here
和西德对决
and fight with Syd.
这就是为什么他带你来这儿
That's why he brought you here.
你看
Look.
你还相信他吗
You still trust him?
- 小维 等等 - 那是真的吗
- Vee, wait. Wait. - Is it true?
什么是不是真的
Is what true?
你带我来这儿也是游戏的一部分
Did you take me here as part of the game?
回答我 是不是
Answer me! Is it true?
你这是在干什么
What are you doing?
事情比你想的要复杂
It's more complicated than that.
今晚一晚上 我和两个最好的朋友决裂了
I just lost my two best friends tonight.
你这么做 能赚多少钱
How much did you get for that?
不不 这和钱无关 好吗
No, no, it's not about the money, all right?
我向你保证 事后我会给你解释的
But I promise I'll explain everything later.
根本没必要解释了 好吗
Just don't even bother, okay?
今晚 西德尼差点死了
I mean, Sydney almost died tonight.
- 我也差点没命 - 我懂 小维 我懂
I almost died tonight. Vee, I know, I know.
这个游戏太变态了 我要去报警
This game is sick. I'm going to the police.
等等 不 不行
Wait, no, no! No!
- 很抱歉 小维 - 你这是在干吗
I'm sorry, vee... What are you doing?
很抱歉 但是你真的不要报警 好吗
I'm sorry, you can't do that, all right?
你不能去报警
You can't go to the police.
为什么不能 就因为我会输了游戏么
Why not? Because I'll lose the game?
不 不是那样的
No, it's not about that!
小维 小维
Vee! Vee!
你不能去报警
You can't go to the police.
你一定会后悔报警的
It's the last thing you wanna do.
小维 你等等 我不是要伤害你
Vee, wait, I wasn't trying to hurt you.
只是事情失控了
It just got outta control.
让开 都让开
Move! Get out of the way!
警察
Officer!
警察 我需要帮助 我
Officer, I need help. I'm...
我在玩一个游戏 它叫玩命直播
I'm playing this game. It's called nerve.
现在 我担心会有人因此而受伤
And I'm worried that someone's gonna get really hurt.
哇 哦
Uh-oh.
告密狗
Snitch!
一个游戏 他们也玩儿么
A game? They playin', too?
对 对
Yeah, yeah.
有人犯罪了么
There's a crime being committed?
没有 但是今晚有一个孩子差点死
了
No, but a kid could die tonight.
看 在这儿 全在我的手机上 你可以看看
Look, here, it's all on my phone. You can see.
什么
What?
怎么回事
告密狗
Snitch!
告密狗受惩罚
Snitches get stitches!
妈妈
Mom?
亲爱的 出了什么事
Honey, what's going on?
妈妈
Mom!
小维 你在哪儿
Vee, where are you?
我们账户里的钱全没了
All the money is missing from our account!
等等 什么
Wait, what?
小维 亲爱的 你现在有麻烦了吗
Vee, honey, are you in trouble?
你能不能 求你了 告诉我究竟怎么回事
Can you just, please, tell me what's going on?
好的 妈妈 我会搞定的 我保证
Okay, mom, I'm gonna fix this, I promise.
搞定什么
Fix what?
喂 小维
Hello? Vee!
- 喂 小维 搞定什么 - 抱歉
Hello? Vee! Fix what? I'm sorry,
但是我要赢得这场游戏
but I gotta win this game.
你好 小维
Hello, vee.
你破坏了游戏规则 现在 你是我们的犯人了
You broke the rules. You are our prisoner.
我们告诉过你不要告密
We told you not to snitch.
现在 你的性命由我们掌握了
Now we control your life.
我们控制你的家庭
We control your family.
控制你的未来
We control your future.
你想全身而退唯一的办法就是赢到最后
The only way out is to win the final round.
去斯塔顿岛码头
Go to the staten island ferry
观众们会找到你
and the watchers will find you.
决赛再见了
See you in the finals.
决赛见 决赛见
See you in the finals. See you in the finals.
去那边看看
Checkin' over here.
我来找你了 小维
I'm comin' for you, vee!
小维 谢天谢地 你还好吗
Vee, thank god! Are you okay?
我还好吗 我糟透了
Am I okay? No, I'm not okay!
你必须和我说实话
You need to tell me everything.
好吗 这他妈究竟是怎么回事
Okay, what the hell is going on?
来这边 这边 这些事为什么会发生在我身上
Come here, come here. Why is this happening to me?
好吧 那个叫泰的家伙
O'Kay, that guy Ty.
去年 我们都在西雅图玩玩命直播
We both played nerve last year in Seattle.
我们挑战
We got a dare to hang from
悬挂在离地200英尺的建筑起重机上
a construction crane 200 feet in the air.
参与的人 有我们俩 还有一个叫罗比的孩子
The two of us and this kid named Robbie.
五 四 三
Five! Four! Three!
行了 罗比 够了 操 他快坚持不住了
Come on, Robbie, that's enough. Shit, he's slipping.
- 二 一 - 哥们 爬回来吧
- Two! One! - Climb back up, man.
- 伊恩 抓住他 - 抓住我的手
- Ian, grab him. - Grab my hand!
我和泰 我们想退出 我们也去找了警察
Ty and I, we bailed and we went to the cops.
我们想结束这个游戏
We tried to get the game shut down,
但是警察什么都不做
but they didn't do anything.
他们就认为这是个意外
No, they just called it an accident.
然后 那些观众 他们
Then the watchers, they...
因为我们告密而追踪我们
They came after us for snitching.
他们害我爸丢了工作
They messed with my dad's job.
在网上泄漏我妹妹的照片
They leaked photos of my sister online.
他们偷走了我们的身份 小维
They stole our identities, vee.
我和泰 我们都成了这个游戏里的犯囚犯
Me and Ty, we became prisoners of the game.
行了 这到底什么意思
Oh, come on. What does that even mean?
那是游戏里的第三种身份
It's the third category.
观众 玩家 囚犯
Watcher, player, prisoner.
我被困在游戏里了
I'm trapped.
解脱的唯一方法 就是赢得游戏
The only way out is to win.
所以 你要赢得游戏
So you have to win.
不不 是你要赢
No. No, you do.
什么
What?
小维 现在你是犯人了
Vee, you're a prisoner now.
你和我 我们要一起赢得最后的决赛
You and I, we're going to the final round together
然后我会输给你
and I'm gonna lose.
什么 你不能那么做
What? No, you can't do that.
就这么定了 就这么定了
It's already done. It's already done.
我要那些观众给我一个挑战
I told the watchers to give me a dare
一个能把泰阻挡在第二位
that's gonna knock Ty outta second place.
那样就只剩下你和我了
It's gonna be me and you.
- 我们得走了 - 不不不
I have to go. No, no, no.
我得带你去个安全的地方 快走
Yeah, I wanna take you somewhere safe. Let's go!
一定还会有别的办法
There has to be another way.
没有别的办法
There isn't.
如果进入决赛的不是我 那就是泰了
If it's not me in the finals, then it's Ty.
为了赢 他会不惜一切代价
And he'll do anything to win.
听我的 我们就这么办
Just tell me we're gonna do this.
维 无权参加
嘿
Hey...
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
我只希望她没事
I just hope she's okay.
- 喂 - 伙计们 是我
- Hello? - Guys, it's me.
天呐 小维 你在哪儿
Oh, my god! Vee, where are you?
停车场
玩命直播 已下线
对不起
I'm so sorry.
没关系 你没事就好
Doesn't matter. I'm just glad you're okay.
- 行了 我们走 我们走吧 - 我不能走
All right, come on. Let's go. I can't.
你说什么
What?
我得完成这个游戏
I have to finish this.
你疯了
Are you insane?
你这是在说什么疯话
What are you talking about?
听着 这个游戏根本不会完
Look, it's never gonna end.
我的意思是 即使他们放过我
I mean, even if they leave me alone,
他们也会找上其他人
they're just gonna do it to somebody else.
就算我们想停 找不到操作人的
We can't stop the game if we wanted to. There's no one to stop.
都是匿名网民
It's just a bunch of anonymous people.
要是他们不是匿名呢
What if they weren't anonymous?
伊恩在挑战一个会把我和他一起送进决赛的挑战
Ian's doing a dare that would put him in the finals.
所以 我就有机会赢他
So it could be me against him.
小维 你真的信任那个家伙么
Vee, do you actually trust this guy?
他是算计你
He is the person who got you
把你拐进这个游戏的人
into this mess in the first place.
是我自己搅进来的
I got me into this mess.
现在 伊恩所做的任何事 都是在帮我
Anything Ian's doing now is to help me get out.
五十名和第六名 再见
去屋顶
我知道 这听起来很不现实 但是我能做到
I know it sounds crazy, but I can do it.
我真的很需要你们的帮助
I just need your help.
你需要我们做什么
What do you need us to do?
汤米 你说过 游戏资源是开放共享的是不是
Tommy, you said the game is open source, right?
你能改变规则么
Do you think you can change the code?
那需要些时间
It's gonna take time.
小西 你能给我们争取时间吗
Syd, could you buy us some?
嘿 爬到吊车上去
Hey. Now climb the crane.
小西
Syd?
怎么了
Yeah?
记住用公共电话
Use a payphone.
啊
Ah!
悬挂五秒钟
下去挂五秒钟
Hang for five seconds.
用一只手挂 用一只手挂
Hang with one hand. Hang with one hand.
靠
Shit!
一 二 三
One! Two! Three!
四
Four!
五
Five!
任务达成
BGM : LUCKY I GOT WHAT I WANT – Jungle
你已进入决赛
请去往F次列车 与观众汇合
- 汤米 这儿都完事儿了 - 我们没多少时间了
- Yeah, it's over here, Tommy. - We don't have a lot of time.
好的 我们马上去 一会儿见
Okay, yeah. We're on our way. We'll see you soon.
怎么样了
How did it go?
起作用了
It went.
起作用了吗
It went?
对 我觉得会奏效的
Yeah. I think it's gonna work.
嗯 最好起作用
Yeah, better work.
我说真是...
I mean, god.
小维上船  观众会找到你的
这是什么地方
What is this place?
全纽约最快的网络
Fastest Internet in New York City.
嘿 汤米
Hey, Tommy!
嘿 hk 我们成功了
Hey, hk, we made it.
那咱们来开始吧 准备好了吗
Let's get this started. You ready?
僵尸网络能干活儿了吗 当然能
Is the botnet up and running? Yeah, of course.
我们把它植入系统就行了
We just gotta enter it into the system.
哦 这位是西德尼 不用多说了
Oh, and this is Sydney. Obviously.
嘿 欢迎来到云端
Hey. Hey. Welcome to the cloud.
你被手撕了 真惨
Sucks you got axed.
好 我们来干掉这个游戏吧
All right. Let's take this game down.
教堂大街
收到了 好的
I got you. Yeah.
维   对  伊恩
决赛
这东西是什么原理
Okay, how's this gonna work?
就像维基百科一样 每个人都能编辑代码
It's like Wikipedia, where anyone can edit the code
但是要获得大众赞同通过
but the majority has to approve it.
而僵尸网络可以当水军
And then the botnet can outvote everyone.
哟 我这可有一众水军待命
Yo, I got a army of bots here waitin' for orders.
嘿 南希 小维在哪儿 这个游戏是什么
Hey, Nancy. Where is vee? What is this game?
别担心 她还好
Don't worry, she's okay.
你要给我解释清楚
I want you to explain it to me.
我给你个地址吧
I'm gonna give you an address.
你来这里见我 我会解释清楚的
Okay, if you meet me here, I'll explain everything.
入场券
Ticket?
你最好快点儿
Better hurry up.
大家伙儿 开始了
Guys, it's starting!
小维 小维 小维 小维
Vee! Vee! Vee! Vee!
玩家们 停下
Players, stop!
后退
Back up.
站定
Stop.
我们有多少水军了
All right, how many bots do we got in?
还不够 但是快够了
Not enough yet, but we are getting there.
玩家们 亮出你们的武器
Players, show us your weapons.
先开枪的获胜
First to shoot wins.
向对手开枪
倒数二十秒
Twenty seconds on the clock.
只有二十秒 Hk 我需要增援
Twenty seconds? Hk, I need backup!
开始 做吧
Begin. Do it.
先把枪举起来吧
Start by just raising your gun.
慢慢把枪举起来就好
Just raise your gun slowly.
开枪射我的肩膀 我会没事的
Then shoot me in the shoulder. I'll be fine.
我怕打偏了 我觉得我不行
What if I miss? I don't know if I can do this.
靠 快闭嘴玩游戏吧
Oh, come on! Just shut up and play the game!
小维 你快做吧 好吗
Vee, you have to hurry, all right?
你必须这么做 只有这样游戏才会结束
You have to do this! This is the only way the game can end.
然后你就能离开了
And then you can walk away.
五
Five,
四
four,
三
three,
二 一
two, one!
呸
Boo!
我做不到
I'm not doing this.
小维 你不能这样
Vee, don't, you can't...
让我来
I'll do it!
卧槽 我们被发现了
Oh, shit. They're onto us.
他们屏蔽掉了我们的外部IP地址
They're blockin' all of our foreign ips!
汤米 做点什么
Tommy, do something!
你们想我了吗
Did y'all miss me?
我说我们再玩一遍冒险吧
And I say we do that dare again.
这回有人准备好好玩儿了
With someone who's really ready to play.
太好了
Yeah!
不要这样 泰 这样做不值得
Don't do it, Ty, it's not worth it, man.
停下 嘿 退后
Stop! Whoa, whoa, back up!
喔喔喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
小白脸 你疯了吧
You have lost your mind, pretty boy!
退回去 你们就想看这个吗
Get back! Is this what you really want?
看我们自相残杀
For us to kill each other?
对 你们想看的就是这个
Yeah! Of course it's what you want!
杀了他们
Kill 'em!
你们觉得这很勇敢吗
You think that takes nerve?
你们怎么不敢把面具摘下来
Why don't you take off your masks
把脸亮出来啊
and show yourselves, huh?
你 把面具摘下来
You, take off your mask.
你叫什么
Yeah, what's your name?
在人堆里面装好汉当然简单了
It's easy for you to be brave in a crowd!
躲在你们的网名后面
Hiding behind your screen names.
你们不明白吗 今天晚上发生的事情
Don't you guys see that you're all still responsible
你们都有责任
for what happens tonight,
尽管你们只是在看
even if you are just watching?
天啊 你们真相信这屁话吗
Oh, my god! Are you really believing this bullshit?
来玩就得赢
Play to win!
Play to win.
你们真的想因为个游戏让我们死吗
You guys really want one of us to die? For a game?
对
Yes!
那打死我吧
Then shoot me.
我看你敢不敢
I dare you.
好吧
Okay.
有谁想让我打死她
Who wants me to shoot her?
小维 你在干什么
Vee, what are you doing?
有谁想让我打死她
Who wants me to shoot her?
汤米 小维在哪儿
Tommy, where's vee?
-好吧 先冷静一下 - 这是什么游戏
- All right, calm down. - What is this game?
我需要答案 你们都在干什么
I want answers! What are you doing?
你们现在告诉我 不然我报警了
You better tell me right now or I'm calling the cops.
不要 南希 不要报警
No! No, Nancy, calm down. No cops.
你们想让我打死她吗
Do you want me to shoot her?
想要打死她 投赞成票
Shoot to kill! Then vote "Yes."
打死她
Shoot to kill!
想要我打死她就投"是"
Vote "Yes" If you want me to shoot her!
不要听他的
Don't listen to him! Say, "No!"
你们想让我打死她吗 想让我打死她吗
You want me to shoot her? You want me to shoot her?
拜托 大家 反对啊
Come on, guys, "No"!
大家 反对啊
Guys, vote "No"!
你 投赞成吧 投赞成
You! Vote "Yes"! Vote "Yes"!
告诉我 投赞成
Let me know! Vote "Yes"!
不要听他的 反对
Don't listen to him! Say, "No!"
来吧 咱们享受一点混乱吧
Come on! Let's have a little bit of anarchy.
好的 我们有办法了
All right, we're getting around them.
IP地址来的更快了
The ips are coming in faster now.
小维 我们得快跑了
Vee, we need to go, right now!
哦天啊
Oh, my god!
好了 没事 大家伙儿继续
Okay, all right. Come on, guys. Keep going.
向维开枪
上帝啊 不要 不要
Oh, my god! No, no, no, it's...
小维 不要啊
Vee, please! Please, please!
不要 不 不 不
No. No, no, no.
能听见我吗 小维 看着我啊
Do you hear me, vee? Look at me, vee, please!
发送吧
Go.
您是
此谋杀的从犯
哥们儿 你收到这个了吗
Dude, are you getting this?
那是我的真名啊
That's my real name.
退 出
是
再见
哇哦
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
不 等等 停下 停下
No, wait, stop, stop!
上帝啊
My god!
没事的 没事的
It's okay, it's okay!
不要 没事了 我还好 没事了
Stop! It's okay. I'm okay. It's okay.
哦天啊
Oh, my god!
不好意思
Sorry.
这是你们一起想出来的
You were in on this?
这是她的计划 她的朋友西德尼打电话给我的
It was her plan, man. Her friend Sydney called me.
所以我来这里了
That's why I'm here.
那把枪是怎么回事
The gun... what?
是空包弹啊
Blanks, bro.
这是假的
It's fake.
哦天啊
Oh, my god!
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
你吓死我了
You scared me.
我们和好了吧
We cool?
对 咱们没事了
Yeah. We're free.
她可真厉害
She's a badass.
你得小心点儿了
Watch out for her.
退出
结束了 最后一名选手出局
That's it. The last player's out.
我们成功了吗
Did we get it?
他们都退出了 以为游戏崩溃了
They're out. Think it's crashing!
我们成功了吧 直播正式结束了
We got it? And nerve is officially offline!
哇 我们戏耍了这场游戏
Wow! We have gamed the game. Whoo!
你们是我见过的最机智的熊孩子了
You guys are the dumbest smart kids I've ever met.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不 不 我才对不起你
No, no, I'm sorry.
我很抱歉把你卷进这些事情
I'm sorry for bringing you into all this.
我真希望我们不是这样认识的
I just wish that we could've met some other way.
我可不是
I don't.
哦 天啊
Oh, man!
你啊
And you.
可真是个大明星
What a rock star.
我应该能把你的钱追回来了
Looks like I can get all your money back.
我这黑客皇后的外号不是白来的
They don't call me hacker kween for nothin'.
是吗 多谢了
Really? Thanks. Yeah.
疯狂的第一次约会 是吧
Crazy first date, huh?
这算是约会吗
Is that what that was?
顺便提一下 我的真名叫萨姆
By the way, my real name is Sam.
嗯 萨姆 认识你真高兴
Well, it's nice to meet you, Sam.
认识你也很高兴 小维
It's nice to meet you, vee.
BGM : CRIME CUTZ – Holy Ghost!!
嘿 小维 纽约二十八度了
Hey, vee, it's 28 degrees in New York!
嗨(｡･∀･)ﾉﾞ  小维
别用手机了
你直接来见我吧
这就去
药丸字幕组倾情译制